const numericalQuizData = [
	{
		id: 11001,
		question: "(2x1÷2), (4÷1x2), (6x1÷2), _____",
		image: "",
		answer: "16",
		choices: [
			"8",
			"12",
			"4",
			"32"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11002,
		question: "(15-8+3), 8, (4÷2x3), ____",
		image: "",
		answer: "4",
		choices: [
			"6",
			"3",
			"8",
			"2"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11003,
		question: "Simplify: 33 1/3 % of 48 + 12 1/2 % of 96 - 44 4/9 % of 27",
		image: "",
		answer: "16",
		choices: [
			"12",
			"18",
			"14",
			"48"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11004,
		question: "12 is 125% of what number?",
		image: "",
		answer: "9.6",
		choices: [
			"7.6",
			"8",
			"9",
			"8.6",
			"10"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11005,
		question: "What percent of 16 is 40?",
		image: "",
		answer: "250%",
		choices: [
			"2.5%",
			"2500%",
			"1/4",
			"25%",
			"40%"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11006,
		question: " 1 ¼ subtracted from its reciprocal is?",
		image: "",
		answer: "-9/20",
		choices: [
			"-4/10",
			"0.45",
			"2.25",
			"-1/5",
			"9/20"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11007,
		question: "What is the ratio of ¼ to 3/5?",
		image: "",
		answer: "5 : 12",
		choices: [
			"1 : 3",
			"3 : 20",
			"2 : 6",
			"3 : 4",
			"5 : 4"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11008,
		question: "What is the difference between √150 and √54?",
		image: "",
		answer: "2 √6",
		choices: [
			"3 √6",
			"16 √6",
			"√96",
			"4 √6",
			"6 √2"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11009,
		question: "A race car travelled for 2 ½ hours with an average speed of 132 5/8 km per hour. Find the total distance it covered.",
		image: "",
		answer: "331 9/16 km",
		choices: [
			"264 5/16 km",
			"332 10/16 km",
			"330 5/16 km",
			"135 1/8 km"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11010,
		question: "99^0 - (-2)^2 + (3^2) - (-4)^2 = ?",
		image: "",
		answer: "-28",
		choices: [
			"-30",
			"-10",
			"-9",
			"30",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11011,
		question: " (100)^0 + (-4^2) - 2^2 = ?",
		image: "",
		answer: "-19",
		choices: [
			"19",
			"-21",
			"13",
			"21",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11012,
		question: "A one fourth percent of a number is 25. What is the number?",
		image: "",
		answer: "10,000",
		choices: [
			"100",
			"1,000",
			"1,000,000",
			"100,000"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11013,
		question: " A mini grocery store has a sale of Php 6435, Php 6927, Php 6855, Php 7230 and Php 6562 for 5 consecutive months. How much sale must he have in the sixth month so that he gets an average sale of Php 6500?",
		image: "",
		answer: "Php 4991",
		choices: [
			"Php 5001",
			"Php 5991",
			"Php 6001",
			"Php 6991"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11014,
		question: "The mean median and mode of 9 numbers are equal. The numbers are 12, 22, 10, 15, 14, 11, 19, 17.	What is the 9th number?",
		image: "",
		answer: "15",
		choices: [
			"14",
			"12",
			"16",
			"18",
			"11"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11015,
		question: "The mean median and mode of 5 numbers are equal. The numbers are 29, 18, 24, 25.	What is the 5th number?",
		image: "",
		answer: "24",
		choices: [
			"26",
			"28",
			"29",
			"18",
			"25"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11016,
		question: "90 increased by what percent of itself gives 180?",
		image: "",
		answer: "100%",
		choices: [
			"50%",
			"90%",
			"150%",
			"200%",
			"130%"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11017,
		question: "If 500 or 25% of graduating class are girls, how many are graduating?",
		image: "",
		answer: "2,000",
		choices: [
			"4,000",
			"3,000",
			"5,000",
			"20,000",
			"10,000"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11018,
		question: "In a group of 8, 000 applicants for a civil service examination, 1600 failed to take the first part of the test. What percent of the total applicants took the first part of the test?",
		image: "",
		answer: "80%",
		choices: [
			"20%",
			"30%",
			"40%",
			"60%"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11019,
		question: "If twice the value of a certain number is increased by 8 the result is 40. What is the number?",
		image: "",
		answer: "16",
		choices: [
			"8",
			"18",
			"24",
			"none of the above",
			"32"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11020,
		question: " Cassy's father was 38 years of age when she was born while her mother was 36 years old when her	brother four years younger to her was born. What is the difference between the ages of her parents?",
		image: "",
		answer: "6 years",
		choices: [
			"2 years",
			"4 years",
			"10 years",
			"8 years"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11021,
		question: "Number Series: 100%, 2, 15/5, 4, ____?",
		image: "",
		answer: "5",
		choices: [
			"2",
			"3",
			"4",
			"6"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11022,
		question: "Number Series: 1/6, 1/3, 1/2, 2/3, ____?",
		image: "",
		answer: "5/6",
		choices: [
			"2/6",
			"2/7",
			"3/5",
			"4/8"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11023,
		question: "Number Series: 250%, 50%, 100%, 20%, 40%, ____?",
		image: "",
		answer: "8%",
		choices: [
			"12%",
			"10%",
			"5%",
			"15%"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11024,
		question: "Number Series: 0.1, 30%, 1/2, 0.7, 90%, ____?",
		image: "",
		answer: "1 1/10",
		choices: [
			"1",
			"100%",
			"7/9",
			"1.4"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11025,
		question: "Number Series: 5, 6, 9, 15, ____, 40",
		image: "",
		answer: "25",
		choices: [
			"21",
			"27",
			"24",
			"33"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11026,
		question: "Number Series: 5,16,49,104,____",
		image: "",
		answer: "181",
		choices: [
			"170",
			"148",
			"115",
			"164"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11027,
		question: "Number Series: 225, 336, 447, ____, 669, 7710",
		image: "",
		answer: "558",
		choices: [
			"114",
			"991",
			"449",
			"338"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11028,
		question: "Number Series: 563,647,479,815,____",
		image: "",
		answer: "143",
		choices: [
			"672",
			"386",
			"279",
			"455"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11029,
		question: "Number Series: 3, 12, 27, 48,75, 108, ____",
		image: "",
		answer: "147",
		choices: [
			"183",
			"192",
			"162",
			"156"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11030,
		question: "Number Series: 0.5, 0.55, 0.65, 0.8,____",
		image: "",
		answer: "1",
		choices: [
			"0.82",
			"0.9",
			"0.95",
			"1.2"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11031,
		question: " 1/2 ÷ 1/4 = ___",
		image: "",
		answer: "More than 1",
		choices: [
			"Less than 1",
			"Equal to 1",
			"Undefined",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11032,
		question: "If Kardo is feeding his buddy 1/2 cup of dog food but uses 1/10 of a cup, how many scoop will he	need to feed his dog?",
		image: "",
		answer: "5 scoops",
		choices: [
			"1/12th scoop",
			"1/20th scoop",
			"4 scoops",
			"3 scoops"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11033,
		question: " If 1 × 10 = 9, 2 × 10 = 18, 3 × 10 = 27, then what is 8 × 10 = ?",
		image: "",
		answer: "72",
		choices: [
			"36",
			"76",
			"78",
			"52"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11034,
		question: "83 : 25 :: 92 : ___?",
		image: "",
		answer: "49",
		choices: [
			"44",
			"51",
			"40",
			"63"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11035,
		question: "72 : 18 :: 56 : ___?",
		image: "",
		answer: "22",
		choices: [
			"24",
			"28",
			"20",
			"16"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11036,
		question: "2 : 12 :: 8 : ___?",
		image: "",
		answer: "18",
		choices: [
			"80",
			"128",
			"396",
			"576"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11037,
		question: "12 : 72 : : 8 : ___?",
		image: "",
		answer: "32",
		choices: [
			"0",
			"42",
			"36",
			"38"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11038,
		question: " PEMDAS: 10÷2x5-(12÷3x4)+1 =__?",
		image: "",
		answer: "10",
		choices: [
			"16",
			"1",
			"-1",
			"23",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11039,
		question: "Sum of all odd numbers between 60 to 120.",
		image: "",
		answer: "2700",
		choices: [
			"3775",
			"3050",
			"4000",
			"2400"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11040,
		question: "John walks everyday from his house to the police station. After walking at a rate of 2 meters/second	for 3 minutes, he looks at his watch and realizes that he has to run 4 meters/second for 1 minute so he won’t be late. What is the distance from his house to the police station?",
		image: "",
		answer: "600m",
		choices: [
			"10m",
			"60m",
			"105m",
			"500m",
			"400m"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11041,
		question: "Radicals: √0.000025",
		image: "",
		answer: "0.005",
		choices: [
			"0.5",
			"0.05",
			"0.00005",
			"0.000005"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11042,
		question: "Number Series: 1/12, 1/6, 1/4, 1/3, ____",
		image: "",
		answer: "5/12",
		choices: [
			"1",
			"1/3",
			"3/6",
			"1/2",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11043,
		question: "A chemist has 400 milliliters of a solution of 20% alcohol on hand, and he wants to mix it with enough pure alcohol to turn it into a 30% alcohol solution. How much pure alcohol will this require?",
		image: "",
		answer: "57",
		choices: [
			"30",
			"40",
			"50",
			"60",
			"48"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11044,
		question: "What is the percentage decrease from 80 to 60?",
		image: "",
		answer: "25%",
		choices: [
			"33.33%",
			"45%",
			"20%",
			"75%",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11045,
		question: "What is the percentage increase from 60 to 80?",
		image: "",
		answer: "33.33%",
		choices: [
			"50%",
			"25%",
			"20%",
			"75%",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11046,
		question: "A businessman sells 60% English books and still has 28 English books. Originally, he had:",
		image: "",
		answer: "70",
		choices: [
			"47",
			"39",
			"60",
			"50",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11047,
		question: "Twelve and one half percent of 200 is what number?",
		image: "",
		answer: "25",
		choices: [
			"112",
			"12",
			"50",
			"45",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11048,
		question: "If the price of a book is first decreased by 25% and then increased by 20%, then the net change in the price will be :",
		image: "",
		answer: "10%",
		choices: [
			"20%",
			"30%",
			"40%",
			"50%",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11049,
		question: "In a mixture 60 litres, the ratio of milk and water 2 : 1. If this ratio is to be 1 : 2, then the quantity of water to be further added is:",
		image: "",
		answer: "60L",
		choices: [
			"20L",
			"30L",
			"40L",
			"70L",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	},
	{
		id: 11050,
		question: " Participants in a certain conference from Luzon, Visayas, and Mindanao are in the ratio of 4:3:2. If there are 120 participants from Luzon, how many participants are there in all?",
		image: "",
		answer: "270",
		choices: [
			"360",
			"150",
			"240",
			"420",
			"None of the above"
		],
		guide: ""
	}
]

export default numericalQuizData;